A Guide to the John Tyler Community College. Office of the President. Correspondence and subject files, 1980-1994
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
John Tyler Community College. Office of the President. Correspondence and subject files, 1980-1994
The Library of Virginia
34744, 34929, 35143, 35465, 35922, 40038
36 cu. ft. (36 boxes)
John Tyler Community College. Office of the President.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Transferred on 12 October 1994 by John Tyler Community College, 13101 Jefferson Davis Highway, Chester, VA 23831 [Acc. 34744].
Transferred on 8 August 1995 by John Tyler Community College, 13101 Jefferson Davis Highway, Chester, VA 23831 [Acc. 34929].
Transferred on 27 September 1996 by John Tyler Community College, 13101 Jefferson Davis Highway, Chester, VA 23831 [Acc. 35143].
Transferred on 8 August 1997 by John Tyler Community College, 13101 Jefferson Davis Highway, Chester, VA 23831 [Acc. 35465].
Transferred on 6 August 1998 by John Tyler Community College, 13101 Jefferson Davis Highway, Chester, VA 23831 [Acc. 35922].
Transferred on 6 September 2002 by John Tyler Community College, 13101 Jefferson Davis Highway, Chester, VA 23831 [Acc. 40038].
Scope and Content
These records consist of the correspondence and subject files of the John Tyler Community College president. Also included are administrative council minutes, 1980-1989 and local board minutes, 1982-1989.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I: Correspondence and subject files, 1980-1989 [Accession 34744]
Series II: Correspondence and subject files, 1982-1990 [Accession 34979]
Series III: Correspondence and subject files, 1990-1991 [Accession 35143]
Series IV: Correspondence and subject files, 1991-1992 [Accession 35465]
Series V: Correspondence and subject files, 1992-1993 [Accession 35922]
Series VI: Correspondence and subject files, 1993-1994 [Accession 40038]
Contents List
- Series I: Correspondence and subject files [Acc. 34744], 1980-1989., Extent: 14 cu. ft. (14 boxes). (Box 1)
  - President's Files, Facilities and Engineering, M-S, 1986 (Box 174)
  - President's Files, Personnel, S-Z, 1986 (Box 175)
  - President's Files, A-L, 1986 (Box 176-1)
  - President's Files, A-L, 1986 (Box 176-2)
  - President's Files, Miscellaneous, 1987 (Box 177)
  - President's Office, Administrative Council Minutes, 1980-1983 (Box 179)
  - President's Office, Administrative Council Minutes, 1984-1989 (Box 180)
  - President's Office, Local Board Minutes, 1987-1989 (Box 181)
  - President's Office, Local Board Minutes, 1982-1986 (Box 182)
  - President's Files, 1988 (Box 183-1)
  - President's Files, 1988 (Box 183-2)
  - President's Files, A-I, 1989 (Box 184)
  - President's Files, J-S, 1989 (Box 185-1)
  - President's Files, J-S, 1989 (Box 185-2)
- Series II: Correspondence and subject files [Acc. 34929], 1982-1990., Extent: 5 cu. ft. (5 boxes). (Box 1)
  - Foundation, Chancellor Search Committee, Master Plan, 1982-1990 (Box 178)
  - President's Files, A-K, 1990 (Box 150-1)
  - President's Files, A-K, 1990 (Box 150-2)
  - President's Files, J-Z, 1990 (Box 151-1)
  - President's Files, J-Z, 1990 (Box 150-2)
- Series III: Correspondence and subject files [Acc. 35143], 1990-1991., Extent: 4 cu. ft. (4 boxes). (Box 1)
  - President's Files, 1990-1991 (Box 328-329)
- Series IV: Correspondence and subject files [Acc. 35465], 1991-1992., Extent: 3 cu. ft. (3 boxes). (Box 1)
  - President's Files, 1991-1992 (Box 363-364)
- Series V: Correspondence and subject files [Acc. 35922], 1992-1993., Extent: 4 cu. ft. (4 boxes). (Box 1)
  - President's Files, A-JTI-B, 1992-1993 (Box 401)
  - President's Files, JT1-B-JT-4, 1992-1993 (Box 401A)
  - President's Files, JT4-V, 1992-1993 (Box 402)
  - President's Files, V-Z, 1992-1993 (Box 402A)
- Series VI: Correspondence and subject files [Acc. 40038], 1993-1994., Extent: 6 cu. ft. (6 boxes). (Box 453-476)
  - President's Files, 1993-1994 (Box 453-454)
  - President's Files, Special correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 455)
  - President's Files, 1993-1994 (Box 476A-B)